whitetailproperties.com 2016-04-10

# Customer Privacy Policy | Whitetail Properties

This Customer Privacy Policy of Whitetail Properties Real Estate, LLC (“Company”) covers the collection, use, and disclosure of personal information that the Company may collect anytime you interact with the Company, such as when you visit our website, when you purchase the Company’s products and services, or when you call our offices. Please take a moment to carefully read the following to learn more about our information practices, including what type of information is gathered, how the information is used and for what purposes, to whom we disclose the information, and how we safeguard your personal information. Your privacy is a priority to us, and we strive to protect it.

## 1\. Reasons the Company Collects Personal Information

We collect your personal information because it helps us deliver a superior level of customer service. It enables us to give you convenient access to our products and services and focus on categories of greatest interest to you. In addition, your personal information helps us keep you posted on the latest product or service announcements, special offers, and events that you might like to hear about.

If you do not want the Company to keep you up to date with our news and the latest information on products and services, simply contact us to update, modify or remove your personal contact information and preferences.

## 2\. Information the Company Collects and How the Information May be Used

There are a number of situations in which your personal information may help us give you better products and services. For example:

We may ask for your personal information when you’re discussing a service issue on the phone with an associate, participating in a survey, registering your products, or purchasing a product.

When you interact with the Company, we may collect personal information relevant to the situation, such as your name, mailing address, phone number, email address, and contact preferences; your billing information and information about the Company products or services you purchase; and information relating to a support or service issue.

We also collect information for market research purposes — such as your occupation and where you use your Company products—to gain a better understanding of our customers and thus provide more valuable service.

We collect information regarding customer activities on our websites. This helps us to determine how best to provide useful information to customers and to understand which parts of our websites, products, and Internet services are of most interest to them.

We may use personal information to provide products and services that you have requested, as well as for auditing, research, and analysis to improve our products and services.

This information may be shared with third parties or in special circumstances as described elsewhere in this policy.

## 3\. Your Online Company ID and Related Information

Our website allows you to create a Whitetail Properties account based on your personal information. This convenient service saves you time and allows for easier use of our web services. In order to create your Whitetail Properties account, you will need to create a personal profile by providing your name, phone number, email address, and in some cases your mailing address or a credit card number. The system saves the information in your personal profile and assigns you your own unique personal Whitetail Properties account which you can use when performing various activities relating to our website and the products and services you purchase from the Company.

## 4\. Gift Cards and Services

The Company also enables you to purchase and send gift certificates and products to family members, friends or colleagues from the online store at whitetailproperties.com . To fulfill your request, the Company may require personal information about the person to whom you are sending the product or service such as their name, physical address, email address, and so on. The personal information you provide about that person is used only for the purpose for which it is collected. The Company will not use the information collected to market directly to that person.

## 5\. When the Company Discloses Your Information

The Company takes your privacy very seriously. The Company does not sell or rent your contact information to other marketers.

To help us provide superior service, your personal information may be shared with legal entities who will take steps to safeguard it in accordance with our privacy policy.

There are also times when it may be advantageous for the Company to make certain personal information about you available to companies that the Company has a strategic relationship with or that perform work for the Company to provide products and services to you on our behalf. These companies may help us process information, extend credit, fulfill customer orders, deliver products to you, manage and enhance customer data, provide customer service, assess your interest in our products and services, or conduct customer research or satisfaction surveys. These companies are prohibited from using your personal information for any unauthorized purposes and are also obligated to protect your information in accordance with the Company’s policies, except if we inform you otherwise at the time of collection. Without such information being made available, it would be difficult for you to purchase products, have products delivered to you, receive customer service, provide us feedback to improve our products and services, or access certain services, offers, and content on our website.

The Company may take the personal information we receive from individuals responding to our customer surveys and combine (or aggregate) it with the responses of other customers we may have to create broader, generic responses to the survey questions (such as gender, age, residence, hobbies, education, employment, industry sector, or other demographic information). The Company may use the aggregated information to improve the quality of its services to you, and to develop new services and products. This aggregated non-personally identifying information may be shared with third parties.

We also reserve the right to disclose your personal information for any reason if, in our sole discretion, we believe that it is reasonable to do so, including credit agencies, collection agencies, merchant database agencies, law enforcement, litigation or to satisfy laws, such as the Electronic Communications Privacy Act, the Child Online Privacy Act, regulations, or governmental or legal requests for such information. We may also disclose personal information that is necessary to identify, contact, or bring legal action against someone who may be violating our contracts, policies and procedures. Finally we may also disclose information about you if we determine that for national security, law enforcement, or other issues of public importance, disclosure is necessary.

## 6\. How the Company Protects Your Personal Information

The Company takes precautions—including administrative, technical, and physical measures—to safeguard your personal information against loss, theft, and misuse, as well as unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration, and destruction.

Our websites use secure encryption on all web pages where personal information is required in order to protect the confidentiality of your personal and credit card information while it’s transmitted over the Internet. You can help us by also taking precautions to protect your personal data when you are on the Internet. Change your passwords often using a combination of letters and numbers, and make sure you use a secure web browser.

While we make every effort to ensure the integrity and security of our network and systems, we cannot guarantee that our security measures will prevent third-party “hackers” from illegally obtaining your personal information.

## 7\. Integrity of Your Personal Information

The Company has safeguards in place to keep your personal information accurate, complete, and up to date for the purposes for which it is used. You always have the right to access and correct the personal information you have provided and can help us ensure that your contact information and preferences are accurate, complete, and up to date by contacting us. In addition, you can request a copy of your personal information, your product registration history, and your interactions with our sales and support agents.

## 8\. Privacy of Children

Protecting children’s privacy is especially important to us. The Company recognizes that parents, guardians, or other adults often purchase our products for family use, including use by minors. We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under 13 for marketing purposes, but because some information is collected electronically, it can appear to be the personal information of the Company purchaser of the product, and will be treated as such by this privacy policy. If a child under 13 submits personal information to the Company and we learn that the personal information is the information of a child under 13, we will attempt to delete the information as soon as possible. It is our policy to comply with the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998 and all other applicable laws. Therefore we restrict our website to persons 18 years or older.

YOU MUST BE EIGHTEEN (18) YEARS OR OLDER TO ACCESS THE COMPANY’S WEBSITE. IF YOU ARE UNDER EIGHTEEN YEARS OF AGE, YOU ARE NOT PERMITTED TO ACCESS THE COMPANY’S WEB SITE FOR ANY REASON. DUE TO THE AGE RESTRICTIONS FOR USE OF THAT WEBSITE, NO INFORMATION OBTAINED BY THAT WEBSITE FALLS WITHIN THE CHILDREN’S ONLINE PRIVACY PROTECTION ACT OF 1998 AND IS NOT MONITORED AS DOING SO.

## 9\. Cookies and Other Technologies

As is standard practice on many corporate websites, our website uses “cookies” and other technologies to help us understand which parts of our websites are the most popular, where our visitors are going, and how much time they spend there. We also use cookies and other technologies to make sure that our online advertising is bringing customers to our products and services. We use cookies and other technologies to study traffic patterns on our website, to make it even more rewarding, as well as to study the effectiveness of our customer communications. We use cookies to customize your experience and provide greater convenience each time you interact with us. If you prefer not to enable cookies, please ask how you can disable cookies. Please note that certain features of our website may not be available once cookies are disabled.

As is true of most websites, we may gather certain information automatically and store it in log files. This information includes Internet Protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, Internet Service Provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and clickstream data. We may use this information, which does not identify individual users, to analyze trends, to administer the site, to track users’ movements around the site and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. The Company will not use the information collected to market directly to that person.

In some of our email messages we may use a “click-through URL” linked to content on our website. When customers click one of these URLs, they pass through our web server before arriving at the destination web page. We may track this click-through data to help us determine interest in particular topics and measure the effectiveness of our customer communications. If you prefer not to be tracked, simply avoid clicking text or graphic links in the email.

In addition, we may use pixel tags—tiny graphic images—to tell us what parts of our website customers have visited or to measure the effectiveness of searches customers perform on our site. Pixel tags also enable us to send email messages in a format customers can read. These also tell us whether emails have been opened to ensure that we’re sending only messages that are of interest to our customers. We may use this information to reduce or eliminate messages sent to a customer. We store all of this information in a secure database.

## 10\. Google Analytics & Advertising Features

We have enabled Google Analytics to collect data about our traffic through the use of Google Advertising cookies and other anonymous identifiers.  An “anonymous identifier” is a random string of characters that is used for the exact same reasons as cookies and are used where cookie technology is not available.This data helps our company better understand our customers and provide website visitors with a more tailored experience. Visitors can opt-out of these features by editing your browser ad settings accordingly. Furthermore, feel free to learn more about Google’s opt-out browser add-on [here](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/).

## 11\. Commitment to Your Privacy

As we said, the Company takes protecting your privacy very seriously. To make sure your personal information is secure, we communicate these guidelines to our employees and strictly enforce privacy safeguards within the company. In addition, the Company supports industry initiatives to preserve privacy rights on the Internet and in all aspects of electronic commerce.

## 12\. Links to Sites of Other Companies

Our website has links to the sites of other companies. We are not responsible for their privacy practices. We encourage you to learn about the privacy policies of those companies.

## 13\. Further Questions Regarding Privacy

If you have questions or concerns about the Company’s Customer Privacy Policy or data processing, please contact us. Feel free to notify us if you do not want us to use your information for a particular purpose.

## 14\. Effective Date; Updates to Privacy Policy

The terms and conditions in this policy statement came into effect February 24, 2013. The Company reserves the right to revise, amend, or modify this policy at any time and in any manner without further notice. Your use of our website and any other services provided by the Company after such changes are implemented constitutes your acknowledgement and acceptance of these changes. Please consult this privacy statement prior to every use for any changes.
